photobox.com 2007-06-17

# Privacy Statement

Privacy Policy 

This privacy policy together with our terms of use sets out how Photobox Limited (“we”, “our”, “us”) will use any personal data we collect from you, or you provide to us during your use of the on-line photo service (the “Website”). 

For the purpose of the Data Protection Act 1998 (the Act), the data controller is Photobox Limited of UNIT 2-3 PARK, ROYAL METRO CENTRE, BRITANNIA WAY, LONDON, NW10 7PA. We may from time to time use data processors, who are not employees, agents or otherwise connected with us, with whom we have an agreement to process your data (“Data Processors”). 

We respect the privacy of every individual who visits the Website. Our policy on the collection and use of personal information is outlined below. 

We collect and use personal information in order to: 

  * administer or otherwise carry out our obligations in relation to any agreement that you may have with us; 
  * anticipate and resolve problems with your service; 
  * carry out market research and the tracking of sales;
  * create and inform you of products and services provided either by us or by carefully selected third parties that you may be interested in, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes and allow Data Processors to do the same.

In order carry out the above, we need to collect and process personal information about you (including but not limited to, your name, address, telephone number, email address, details of your visits to the Website and any transactional information in relation to order fulfilment). We may ask you for this information on the Website during the registration process or at any subsequent point. The data we collect may be provided to Data Processors for analysis so that we may tailor the goods, services and marketing materials we, and other third parties offer to you (where you have consented to receive the same). 

In order to take advantage of some of our services, you may need to supply us with the personal details of a third party (for example, their name and address if you wish to send them some prints). We will not use this information for anything other than providing the service for which the information was supplied. 

We will not disclose any personally identifiable information without your permission unless: 

  * we are legally entitled to do so (for example, pursuant to a court order or for the purposes of prevention of crime or fraud). You will be treated as having given your permission for disclosures referred to in this policy;
  * we are in negotiations with a third party for the sale or purchase of any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets;
  * if we, or substantially all of our assets, are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets; and
  * to enforce or apply our terms of use and other agreements; or to protect our rights, property, safety, customers, or others.

If you do not wish to receive mailings from us and/or from our partners, please access the "My Details" area from your home page on the Website and ensure that the box for promotional mailings is turned off. 

Non-personal details 

We may automatically collect non-personal information about you, such as the type of browsers you use or the Website from which you linked to us. This information is only used to assist us in providing an effective service on the Website. We may, from time to time, supply the owners and operators of third party websites which have a link to our site with information about the number of users linking to the Website from their website. You cannot be identified from any of this information. 

Competitions 

From time to time, we may hold competitions via the Website. When you enter a competition, we may ask you to tell us your name, email address, mailing address and telephone number. We will collect and use these details in accordance with the provisions of this privacy policy 

Cookies 

We may collect information about your computer, including where available your IP address, operating system and browser type, for system administration and to report information to our branded partners. 

We may store some information on your computer when you visit the Website. This information facilitates your use of the Website, and ensures that you do not need to re-enter your details on each visit. The information may be stored in a cookie which is required for the shopping basket and other e-commerce facilities to function. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, which allows you to choose whether or not to accept it, however switching off cookies may result in the Website having dramatically reduced functionality including but not limited to being able to shop on the site. To find out how to enable/disable cookies, please [click here](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies). We do not have any control over cookies which our advertisers or branded partners may use on the Website. 

Accuracy 

We aim to keep our records as accurate as possible. If you would like to review or change the details that you have supplied us with at any time you can either amend your details directly by going to the ‘My Details’ section of your Home Page of the Website, or by contacting us using the details below. 

Security 

The technology that we use and the policies that we have implemented are intended to safeguard your privacy from unauthorised access and improper use. We will continue to update these measures as new technology becomes available. 

Your rights 

You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. We will usually inform you (before collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for such purposes or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by checking certain boxes on the forms we use to collect your data or by going to the ‘My Preferences’ area of the ‘My Details’ section of your Home Page of the Website. You can also exercise the right at any time by contacting us. 

Access to Information 

The Act gives you the right to access information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with the Act. Any access request may be subject to a fee of £10 to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you. 

Links 

Our site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites. 

Contact us 

If you would like to contact us click here.
